Amin Hasanzadeh

Full Stack Developer

Profile

I have over 3 years of experience in software development, covering front-end design, back-end development, project estimating, technical design, documentation, testing, deployments, and client support. My dedication has helped create successful applications for diverse clients.

Experience

Full Stack Developer

07/2022 - 08/2023

Bahar Afagh Shargh

- Enhanced truck performance and 1000+ owners' satisfaction with smart features.
- Improved performance and security by offloading about 50% microcontroller tasks in various areas.
- Created a real-time hardware communication socket and improved device tracking with an optimized web panel, saving time up to days.
- Optimized Flutter app performance with GetX state management up.

Full Stack Developer

04/2022 - 03/2023

Medis Holding

- Delivered dynamic web apps, mainly focusing on Angular, including Charaneh, a widely-used poetry site in Iran.
- Contributed to HTML/CSS/JavaScript project Painverse, showcasing tele-robotic products.
- Improved Alobodo Flutter app which is used by 1000+ technicians and 6000+ users, with Firebase push notifications.
- Demonstrated expertise in Django, Flutter, and Angular development.

Flutter Developer

04/2021 - 08/2021

Yadak Pro

- Led the development of a specialized e-commerce app for 1000+ bulk car part buyers, demonstrating proficiency in Flutter.
- Designed an intuitive interface with advanced filtering and search features, enhancing user engagement.
- Enabled seamless order submissions with real-time SMS notifications
- Gained backend development experience in PHP

Flutter Developer

04/2021 - 08/2021

Artin Analysis LTD

- Contributed as a Flutter developer to the international app Rapidrops, serving both couriers and passengers.
- Improved passenger experience with courier service request features.
- Used agile methods and Bloc state management to optimize team and app performances.
- Enhanced app development and project management skills through valuable experience.

Wordpress Developer

01/2020 - 02/2021

Yadak Pro

- Led a WordPress-based car parts e-commerce project.
- Contributed to e-commerce, refining WordPress skills.
- Demonstrated WordPress proficiency in project execution.
- Enhanced e-commerce and web development skills.



Contact

aminhasanzadeh1999@gmail.com



+358-41-725-7439



in Linkedin/amin-hasanzadeh



Website



github.com/aminhm

Education

2017 - 2022

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

Shiraz University – Iran

2023 - Present

Master of Science in Software Engineering

LUT University - Finland

Skills

Front-end

HTML5, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, Angular, Flutter, WordPress, TypeScript, Bootstrap

Backend

Django development, API development (REST), Python Development

Database and Server

MySQL, PostgreSQL, Nginx, Gunicorn

Version Controller

Agile Methodologies, Scrum, Jira, Trello